<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- eng -->
<Resource xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns="urn:ComolTranslation">
  <item name="LblFunzione.Text" description="Funzionalità" html="false" placeholder="false">Function</item>
  <item name="LblNote.Text" html="true" placeholder="false">&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; NOTE &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;P&gt; The developers and editors of the site are not responsible for the contents of the files entered by the users. &lt;br&gt; for the modification or cancellation of the same. &lt;br&gt; It is however kept track of the file name, the user name and the time when the file was uploaded. The files are also visible to all participants in the chat. It is therefore advisable to encrypt confidential documents. &lt;br&gt; Remember that it is a good idea to compress files to take up less space and reduce upload and download times. &lt;br&gt; Also files with extension &lt;b&gt; * .com &lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt; *. exe &lt;/b&gt; are renamed to &lt;b&gt; respectively *. co_ &lt;/b&gt; and &lt; b&gt; *. ex_ &lt;/b&gt; To run these files you need to download them and rename the extension. We recommend that you check them with an antivirus before doing so. &lt;/P&gt;</item>
  <item name="LblPuls1.Text" html="false" placeholder="false">View file informations: name, size, by whom has been uploaded, upload date.</item>
  <item name="LblPuls2.Text" html="false" placeholder="false">Display a list of links from which download the wanted files</item>
  <item name="LblPuls3.Text" html="false" placeholder="false">Delete selected files. Once deleted, a file can not be recover. After a certain period, it will be automatically deleted.</item>
  <item name="LblPuls4.Text" html="false" placeholder="false">Opens this screen</item>
  <item name="LblPuls5.Text" html="true" placeholder="false">Upload the selected file to the server.&lt;br&gt;For security reasons, the file extension *.exe will be renamed as *.ex_ and the extension *.com as *.co_</item>
  <item name="LblPuls6.Text" html="false" placeholder="false">Select file to upload.</item>
  <item name="LblPuls7.Text" html="false" placeholder="false">It is impossible to load a file. Maybe another user is uploading a file or the maximum number of files has been reached.</item>
  <item name="LblPuls8.Text" html="false" placeholder="false">Indicates that is possible to load another file.</item>
  <item name="LblPuls9.Text" html="false" placeholder="false">Update list of available files</item>
  <item name="LblPuls10.Text" html="false" placeholder="false">Available file list.</item>
  <item name="LblTasto.Text" description="Pulsante" html="false" placeholder="false">Key</item>
</Resource>